<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Abolfazl Hashemi</title>
    <link>https://abolfazlh.github.io/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://abolfazlh.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Abolfazl Hashemi</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>©`2020` - Abolfazl Hashemi</copyright>
    <image>
      <url>https://abolfazlh.github.io/img/icon-192.png</url>
      <title>Abolfazl Hashemi</title>
      <link>https://abolfazlh.github.io/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title> </title>
      <link>https://abolfazlh.github.io/mypubs/pubs_type_not_subject/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://abolfazlh.github.io/mypubs/pubs_type_not_subject/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;preprint&#34;&gt;Preprint&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Chen, Y., Hashemi, A., Vikalo, H., &lt;strong&gt;Communication-Efficient Algorithms for Distributed Optimization Over Directed Graphs,&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;Submitted&lt;/em&gt;, 2020.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hashemi, A, Vikalo, H., de Veciana, G., &lt;strong&gt;Progressive Stochastic Greedy Sparse Reconstruction and Support Selection,&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;Submitted&lt;/em&gt;, 2020.
&lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/abs/1907.09064&#34;&gt;(Link)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ghasemi, M., Hashemi, A., Vikalo, H., Topcu, U., &lt;strong&gt;Online Learning in Adversarial Markov Decision Processes: Some Regret Bounds,&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;Submitted&lt;/em&gt;, 2020.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hashemi, A., Shafipour, R., Vikalo, H., Mateos, G., &lt;strong&gt;Accelerated Sampling of Bandlimited Graph Signals,&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;Submitted&lt;/em&gt;, 2019.
&lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/abs/1807.07222&#34;&gt;(Link)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;journal-papers&#34;&gt;Journal Papers&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hashemi, A., Ghasemi, M., Vikalo, H., Topcu, U., &lt;strong&gt;Randomized greedy sensor selection: Leveraging weak submodularity,&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;IEEE Transactions on Automatic Control&lt;/em&gt;, To appear, 2020.
&lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/abs/1807.08627&#34;&gt;(Link)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hashemi, A. and  Vikalo, H., &lt;strong&gt;Evolutionary Self-Expressive Models for
Subspace Clustering,&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;IEEE Journal of Selected Topics in Signal Processing,&lt;/em&gt; vol. 12, no. 6, pp. 1534&amp;ndash;1546, Dec. 2018.
&lt;a href=&#34;https://ieeexplore.ieee.org/stamp/stamp.jsp?arnumber=8502063&#34;&gt;(Link)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hashemi, A. and Vikalo, H., &lt;strong&gt;Accelerated Orthogonal Least-Squares for Large-Scale Sparse Reconstruction,&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;Digital Signal Processing,&lt;/em&gt; vol. 82, pp. 91&amp;ndash;105, Nov. 2018.
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S1051200418305311&#34;&gt;(Link)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hashemi, A., Zhu, B., Vikalo, H., &lt;strong&gt;Sparse Tensor Decomposition for Haplotype Assembly of Diploids and Polyploids,&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;BMC Genomics,&lt;/em&gt; vol. 19, no. 4, pp. 1&amp;ndash;15, Mar. 2018.
&lt;a href=&#34;https://bmcgenomics.biomedcentral.com/articles/10.1186/s12864-018-4551-y&#34;&gt;(Link)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;conference-papers&#34;&gt;Conference Papers&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ghasemi, M., Hashemi, A., Vikalo, H., Topcu, U., &lt;strong&gt;Identifying Low-Dimensional Structures in Markov Chains: A Nonnegative Matrix Factorization Approach,&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;American Control Conference (ACC)&lt;/em&gt;, Denver, CO, July 2020.
&lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/abs/1909.12898&#34;&gt;(Link)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ghasemi, M., Hashemi, A., Vikalo, H., Topcu, U., &lt;strong&gt;On Submodularity of Quadratic Observation Selection in Constrained Networked Sensing Systems,&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;American Control Conference (ACC),&lt;/em&gt; Philadelphia, PA, July 2019.
&lt;a href=&#34;https://ieeexplore.ieee.org/stamp/stamp.jsp?arnumber=8814899&#34;&gt;(Link)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shafipour, R., Hashemi, A., Mateos, G., Vikalo, H., &lt;strong&gt;Online topology inference from streaming stationary graph signals,&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;IEEE Data Science Workshop (DSW)&lt;/em&gt;, Minneapolis, MN, June  2019.
&lt;a href=&#34;https://ieeexplore.ieee.org/stamp/stamp.jsp?tp=&amp;amp;arnumber=8755560&#34;&gt;(Link)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hashemi, A., Ghasemi, M., Vikalo, H., Topcu, U., &lt;strong&gt;Submodular Observation Selection and Information Gathering for Quadratic Models,&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;International Conference on Machine Learning (ICML)&lt;/em&gt;, Long Beach, CA, June 2019.
&lt;a href=&#34;http://proceedings.mlr.press/v97/hashemi19a/hashemi19a.pdf&#34;&gt;(Link)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hashemi, A. and Vikalo, H., &lt;strong&gt;Evolutionary Subspace Clustering: Discovering Structure In Self-expressive Time-series Data,&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;International Conference on Acoustic, Speech and Signal Processing (ICASSP),&lt;/em&gt; Brighton, UK, May 2019.
&lt;a href=&#34;https://ieeexplore.ieee.org/stamp/stamp.jsp?arnumber=8682405&#34;&gt;(Link)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Consul, S., Hashemi, A., Vikalo, H., &lt;strong&gt;A MAP Framework for Support Recovery of Sparse Signals Using Orthogonal Least Squares,&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;International Conference on Acoustic, Speech and Signal Processing (ICASSP),&lt;/em&gt; Brighton, UK, May 2019.
&lt;a href=&#34;https://ieeexplore.ieee.org/stamp/stamp.jsp?arnumber=8683151&#34;&gt;(Link)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hashemi, A., Kilic, O.F., Vikalo, H., &lt;strong&gt;Near-Optimal Distributed Estimation for a Network of Sensing Units Operating Under Communication Constraints,&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;Conference on Decision and Control (CDC),&lt;/em&gt; Miami, FL, Dec. 2018.
&lt;a href=&#34;https://ieeexplore.ieee.org/stamp/stamp.jsp?arnumber=8618717&#34;&gt;(Link)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hashemi, A., Shafipour, R., Vikalo, H., Mateos, G., &lt;strong&gt;A Novel Scheme for Support Identification and Iterative Sampling of Bandlimited Graph Signals,&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;Global Conference on Signal and Information Processing (GlobalSIP),&lt;/em&gt; Anaheim, CA, Nov. 2018.
&lt;a href=&#34;https://ieeexplore.ieee.org/stamp/stamp.jsp?tp=&amp;amp;arnumber=8646488&#34;&gt;(Link)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hashemi, A., Ghasemi, M., Vikalo, H., Topcu, U., &lt;strong&gt;A Randomized Greedy Algorithm for Near-Optimal Sensor Scheduling in Large-Scale Sensor Networks,&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;American Control Conference (ACC),&lt;/em&gt; Milwaukee, WI, Jun. 2018. 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://ieeexplore.ieee.org/stamp/stamp.jsp?arnumber=8431563&#34;&gt;(Link)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hashemi, A., Shafipour, R., Vikalo, H., Mateos, G., &lt;strong&gt;Sampling and Reconstruction of Graph Signals via Weak Submodularity and Semidefinite Relaxation,&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;International Conference on Acoustic, Speech and Signal Processing (ICASSP),&lt;/em&gt; Calgary, Alberta, Canada, Apr. 2018.
&lt;a href=&#34;https://ieeexplore.ieee.org/stamp/stamp.jsp?arnumber=8461925&#34;&gt;(Link)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hashemi, A. and Vikalo, H., &lt;strong&gt;Sparse Recovery via Branch and Bound Least-Squares,&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;International Conference on Acoustic, Speech and Signal Processing (ICASSP),&lt;/em&gt; New Orleans, LA, Mar. 2017.
&lt;a href=&#34;https://ieeexplore.ieee.org/stamp/stamp.jsp?arnumber=7953060&#34;&gt;(Link)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hashemi, A. and Vikalo, H., &lt;strong&gt;Sparse Linear Regression via Generalized Orthogonal Least-Squares,&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;Global Conference on Signal and Information Processing (GlobalSIP),&lt;/em&gt; Washington, DC, Dec. 2016.
&lt;a href=&#34;https://ieeexplore.ieee.org/stamp/stamp.jsp?tp=&amp;amp;arnumber=7906052&#34;&gt;(Link)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;workshops&#34;&gt;Workshops&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hashemi, A., Zhu, B., Vikalo, H., &lt;strong&gt;Sparse Tensor Decomposition for Haplotype Assembly of Diploids and Polyploids,&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;The 4th International Workshop on Computational Network Biology: Modeling, Analysis, Control (CNB-MAC),&lt;/em&gt; Boston, MA, Aug. 2017.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hashemi, A., Zhu, B., Vikalo, H., &lt;strong&gt;A Tensor Factorization Framework for Haplotype Assembly of Diploids and Polyploids,&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;RECOMB Satellite Workshop on Massively Parallel Sequencing,&lt;/em&gt; Hong Kong, May 2017.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
